<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- RevitPy Group Policy Administrative Template -->
<policyDefinitionResources xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" revision="1.0" schemaVersion="1.0" xmlns="http://schemas.microsoft.com/GroupPolicy/2006/07/PolicyDefinitions">
  <displayName>RevitPy Administrative Template</displayName>
  <description>Administrative template for managing RevitPy deployment and configuration</description>

  <resources>
    <stringTable>
      <!-- Category Names -->
      <string id="RevitPy">RevitPy</string>
      <string id="RevitPy_Installation">Installation</string>
      <string id="RevitPy_Configuration">Configuration</string>
      <string id="RevitPy_Security">Security</string>
      <string id="RevitPy_Updates">Updates</string>

      <!-- Installation Policies -->
      <string id="AutoInstall">Automatically install RevitPy</string>
      <string id="AutoInstall_Help">
        This policy setting allows you to configure automatic installation of RevitPy on domain computers.

        If you enable this policy setting, RevitPy will be automatically installed on computers during startup or user logon.

        If you disable or do not configure this policy setting, RevitPy will not be automatically installed.
      </string>

      <string id="InstallPath">RevitPy installation path</string>
      <string id="InstallPath_Help">
        This policy setting allows you to specify the installation path for RevitPy.

        If you enable this policy setting, RevitPy will be installed to the specified path.

        If you disable or do not configure this policy setting, RevitPy will be installed to the default path (C:\Program Files\RevitPy).
      </string>

      <string id="RevitVersions">Supported Revit versions</string>
      <string id="RevitVersions_Help">
        This policy setting allows you to specify which Revit versions should have RevitPy integration enabled.

        If you enable this policy setting, RevitPy add-ins will be configured for the specified Revit versions only.

        If you disable or do not configure this policy setting, RevitPy will be configured for all detected Revit versions.
      </string>

      <!-- Configuration Policies -->
      <string id="ConfigurationFile">Organization configuration file</string>
      <string id="ConfigurationFile_Help">
        This policy setting allows you to specify a centralized configuration file for RevitPy.

        If you enable this policy setting, RevitPy will use the specified configuration file and users will not be able to modify certain settings.

        If you disable or do not configure this policy setting, RevitPy will use default configuration settings.
      </string>

      <string id="LogLevel">Logging level</string>
      <string id="LogLevel_Help">
        This policy setting allows you to configure the logging level for RevitPy.

        If you enable this policy setting, RevitPy will log messages according to the specified level:
        - Error: Only error messages
        - Warning: Error and warning messages
        - Information: Error, warning, and informational messages
        - Debug: All messages including detailed debugging information

        If you disable or do not configure this policy setting, RevitPy will use the default logging level (Information).
      </string>

      <string id="EnableTelemetry">Enable telemetry</string>
      <string id="EnableTelemetry_Help">
        This policy setting allows you to control whether RevitPy collects and sends telemetry data.

        If you enable this policy setting, RevitPy will collect usage statistics and error reports.

        If you disable this policy setting, RevitPy will not collect any telemetry data.

        If you do not configure this policy setting, users can choose whether to enable telemetry.
      </string>

      <!-- Security Policies -->
      <string id="CodeSigningRequired">Require code signing</string>
      <string id="CodeSigningRequired_Help">
        This policy setting allows you to require that all RevitPy scripts and add-ins be digitally signed.

        If you enable this policy setting, RevitPy will only execute signed code from trusted publishers.

        If you disable or do not configure this policy setting, RevitPy will execute both signed and unsigned code.
      </string>

      <string id="TrustedPublishers">Trusted code publishers</string>
      <string id="TrustedPublishers_Help">
        This policy setting allows you to specify a list of trusted publishers for RevitPy code.

        If you enable this policy setting, RevitPy will only execute code signed by the specified publishers.

        If you disable or do not configure this policy setting, RevitPy will accept code from any publisher.
      </string>

      <string id="SandboxMode">Enable sandbox mode</string>
      <string id="SandboxMode_Help">
        This policy setting allows you to enable sandbox mode for RevitPy script execution.

        If you enable this policy setting, RevitPy scripts will run in a restricted environment with limited system access.

        If you disable or do not configure this policy setting, RevitPy scripts will run with normal privileges.
      </string>

      <!-- Update Policies -->
      <string id="AutoUpdate">Enable automatic updates</string>
      <string id="AutoUpdate_Help">
        This policy setting allows you to control automatic updates for RevitPy.

        If you enable this policy setting, RevitPy will automatically check for and install updates.

        If you disable this policy setting, RevitPy will not check for updates automatically.

        If you do not configure this policy setting, users can choose whether to enable automatic updates.
      </string>

      <string id="UpdateChannel">Update channel</string>
      <string id="UpdateChannel_Help">
        This policy setting allows you to specify which update channel RevitPy should use.

        If you enable this policy setting, RevitPy will receive updates from the specified channel:
        - Stable: Tested, stable releases
        - Beta: Pre-release versions with new features
        - Dev: Development builds (not recommended for production)

        If you disable or do not configure this policy setting, RevitPy will use the Stable channel.
      </string>

      <string id="UpdateServer">Update server URL</string>
      <string id="UpdateServer_Help">
        This policy setting allows you to specify a custom update server for RevitPy.

        If you enable this policy setting, RevitPy will check for updates from the specified server.

        If you disable or do not configure this policy setting, RevitPy will use the default update server.
      </string>

      <!-- Value Options -->
      <string id="LogLevel_Error">Error</string>
      <string id="LogLevel_Warning">Warning</string>
      <string id="LogLevel_Information">Information</string>
      <string id="LogLevel_Debug">Debug</string>

      <string id="UpdateChannel_Stable">Stable</string>
      <string id="UpdateChannel_Beta">Beta</string>
      <string id="UpdateChannel_Dev">Development</string>
    </stringTable>

    <presentationTable>
      <!-- Text input presentations -->
      <presentation id="InstallPath_Presentation">
        <textBox refId="InstallPath_TextBox">
          <label>Installation path:</label>
          <defaultValue>C:\Program Files\RevitPy</defaultValue>
        </textBox>
      </presentation>

      <presentation id="RevitVersions_Presentation">
        <textBox refId="RevitVersions_TextBox">
          <label>Revit versions (comma-separated):</label>
          <defaultValue>2022,2023,2024,2025</defaultValue>
        </textBox>
      </presentation>

      <presentation id="ConfigurationFile_Presentation">
        <textBox refId="ConfigurationFile_TextBox">
          <label>Configuration file path:</label>
        </textBox>
      </presentation>

      <presentation id="TrustedPublishers_Presentation">
        <listBox refId="TrustedPublishers_List">Trusted Publishers:</listBox>
      </presentation>

      <presentation id="UpdateServer_Presentation">
        <textBox refId="UpdateServer_TextBox">
          <label>Update server URL:</label>
          <defaultValue>https://updates.revitpy.com</defaultValue>
        </textBox>
      </presentation>

      <!-- Dropdown presentations -->
      <presentation id="LogLevel_Presentation">
        <dropdownList refId="LogLevel_DropDown" noSort="true" defaultItem="2">Logging Level:</dropdownList>
      </presentation>

      <presentation id="UpdateChannel_Presentation">
        <dropdownList refId="UpdateChannel_DropDown" noSort="true" defaultItem="0">Update Channel:</dropdownList>
      </presentation>
    </presentationTable>
  </resources>
</policyDefinitionResources>
